This is Ranma of the Saotome
School of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
And this is Akane from the Tendo Dojo.
These two teens were arranged
to be married by their parents.
Don't tell me what to do.
You're such a pain in the butt.
Unfortunately,
Ranma has a bit of a problem.
What the hell, man?
Whenever he's splashed with cold water,
he changes into a girl.
RANMA1/2
KOLKHOZ HIGH SCHOOL
- The Charlotte Cup?
- What's that about?
I'LL NEVER LET GO
- Sanzenin's going to be in this.
- Ooh! We've got to go cheer him on.
What's all this Charlotte Cup crap?
It's getting ridiculous now.
No matter what happens,
Akane and I will get to pair together
for this match,
and we'll win!
Oh, I was looking everywhere for you,
"Charlotte."
If I'm the one pairing up with Akane,
I'll be unbeatable.
So just sit back and watch
from the stands, okay?
MARTIAL SKATING
BOYS' DRESSING ROOM
Hmm.
Perfect, as usual.
Hmm?
Oh. Hey, my corny sex pest.
It's Mikado Sanzenin!
Have you healed up
from all the hits you took?
Huh. I might have allowed my guard
to slip the other day.
But an official match is going to play out
very differently.
So, your partner...
It's Akane Tendo, if I recall?
Uh...
I don't believe I've had the chance
to greet her properly.
What does that mean?
I'll state this for the record.
The sweet lips of Akane Tendo will be
mine to steal and smother
the second you lose our match.
What the hell did you say?
Do you have the ability to think about
anything else, or is this it, you creeper?
Look inside my mind.
You'll find it's full of such genius.
This guy's freakin' weird.
I guess
someone's talking about me.
Huh.
There's palpable excitement in the air
here at the Kolkhoz High School ice rink.
Students are pouring into the venue
so that they may bear witness
to the apocalyptic showdown
that is only moments away.
The fateful Charlotte Cup match,
which pits Kolkhoz and Furinkan
High Schools against each other,
is about to begin.
This will be a battle on ice.
These chilling vibes are reminiscent
of Alexander Nevsky's historic clash
from 1242, before defeating his invaders
on a frozen lake.
Will it be Kolkhoz or Furinkan High School
to seize victory today and go on
to become the modern Nevsky?
This is live commentary,
provided by the team you love,
Ichiro and the Furinkan Radio Club.
They've just lowered the lights
to give both teams
the chance to enter the rink.
The golden pair of Martial Skating,
Azusa Shiratori and Mikado Sanzenin,
make their entrance!
It's Sanzenin!
Azusa! Azusa!
Hmm. Do they have to make
this big of a deal with their entrance?
I know, right?
Try not to get too close to Sanzenin
if you can.
Hmm? What are you talking about?
How am I supposed to attack him
if I can't get close?
Okay, but still...
Come on. We're making our entrance next.
Mmm.
All right, then we can be flashy too!
Time for us to go out
and stun 'em with our skills!
Wait a second, Ranma!
Ah! Here we go.
Akane and Ranma are now on the ice.
Their entrance is absolutely stunning.
Argh! Stop! Stop!
Whoa!
Argh! Shut your mouth!
The way I'm seeing it, Charlotte is
totally going to come home with me today.
You're wrong!
I'm never gonna let you take P-chan.
The match is starting.
A pet pig's fate hangs in the balance.
This no-holds-barred match will be
a single round ending in a knockout.
- We can win this if we get the first hit!
- Yeah.
Both pairs are off
to a smooth start.
The Furinkan team releases
a death spiral kick.
Huh?
- You look particularly cute today.
- Ugh.
Oh! We know this one, folks!
Sanzenin's going straight for
his special Kiss Attack!
Ew!
Not on my watch!
- Ranma, look out!
- Huh?
It's a surprise diving knee drop!
That looks like it hurt!
Ranma!
I finally have you to myself.
Get lost!
Poor girl. There's no need to play shy.
That kiss was yours to keep.
She's looking pretty grossed-out to me.
You know, I could really use
your help here.
The more rejection I come to face,
the more motivated I become.
I'll do anything to steal those lips!
Akane, stay out of the way.
The Furinkan pair performs
a throw jump!
In a flash,
he landed a right straight!
Fence! Fence! Fence! Fence!
Yeah, I know!
You gotta stop now!
I wish I could!
That's a heck of a backflip!
Whoa!
Oh! Hey, does doing this hurt?
How about now? Does this hurt?
What about now?
Does it hurt now?
You can tell me if it hurts.
Stop jabbing me in that spot,
you stupid girl!
It's only 'cause I'm so worried about you,
you know?
Huh?
I have to admit that was a surprise.
You hurt me enough to take a knee.
If you try to put your greasy mitts
all over Akane again,
you're gonna need a lot more
than taking a knee.
Oh. What will you do to me?
Ugh. I'll knock you into a coffin.
Listen up! Akane is already engaged to me.
And if you touch her again,
I'll kill you.
Does he really mean that?
Huh. She's your fiancée, huh?
So you're not married yet.
How convenient for me.
I still have a chance
to rip apart your bond.
We might be the golden pair
of Martial Skating,
but we're also known by another name...
The Bone-Chilling
Matchbreakers on Ice!
That's right.
Sanzenin and Shiratori unleash
their ultimate technique,
the Couple Crusher!
No couple has ever survived this attack.
At least not without having
a nasty public break-up first!
Till us, that is. You ready?
Uh, yeah.
Try and stay focused.
Mmm?
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
I'm winning the match.
Whoa.
Well, there it is!
This is the terrifying Couple Crusher.
It's a nasty-looking
Farewell Merry-go-Round.
All you have to do is let go,
and then I stop the spinning.
Yes. Like hell I will!
Just let go of me, Ranma.
No, idiot, you'll get slammed if I do.
He can only be saved if he betrays
his partner and lets go of her.
Let my hands go already.
After I heard what he said
I'm never letting go.
Huh. The deeper your trust in each other,
the greater your sense of betrayal
when your partner lets go.
Any couple unlucky enough to be caught
in the Farewell Merry-go-Round
is doomed to break up.
You don't have to believe
what he says.
I'll be fine, so just let go.
No, you dummy!
I'm not about to let you fly solo.
- You're too stupid to be left alone.
- What... What did you say?
I'm, like, getting so tired now.
I'm done with this.
Through all of it,
he never let go of her hand.
The Farewell Merry-go-Round
has been defeated!
Although it seems like he took
a lot of damage.
Can Ranma Saotome get back on his feet?
Idiot! You had to show off.
You didn't have to take it this far.
Ranma?
Are you okay, Ranma?
If I were to guess,
every bone in his body is probably broken.
If he survived that he'd be a monster.
He did all this for me...
Ranma, why are you so stupid?
Come on!
Is it really that hard for you
to throw out a "sorry" or a "thank you"?
- Mmm?
- You were faking it?
Okay, but who's the idiot now?
Dummy. I was worried about you.
Huh. You really think
something like that could take me out?
It hurts...
So you got up.
Yeah. This match is just gettin' started.
The match is resuming.
The Charlotte Cup battle
over the fate of a pig.
Which of these young pairs will win?
Hey, the pig is missing.
What?
Charlotte, no.
Eh? Oh. The little piggy went missing?
- Where could he be?
- Hmph. Now it's finally my turn.
You're proving to be
quite a tough nut to crack, aren't you?
Sure am. And I'm
only getting started, Sanzenin.
Hang on. You shouldn't be fighting
in this condition.
I don't wanna hear it.
I'm gonna grab
that weirdo and smash his face.
You're welcome to try.
I can't have you withdraw from the match.
Not before one thing.
I steal a kiss from Akane, just as I pro--
My poor little Charlotte's gone missing!
Why the hell would you do that,
you buffoon?
I want to find Charlotte!
Let's get back out there.
Huh? Hold it right there.
- Huh?
- Hmm.
What the hell did you do that for?
You can't keep pushing yourself.
Please withdraw.
Uh...
Uh, what?
A power outage?
What's going on?
Did someone cut the lights?
Huh?
Be a girl so you can sit back and watch.
Come on, Akane, we can be a pair.
Things were going so well
until you showed up, you bastard.
What's going on now?
Argh! What just happened?
Furinkan High School's pair!
It appears they've been
completely swapped out!
You're not the one
who's supposed to be here.
You're the dumbass
who kept me out here in the first place.
- Take that! And that!
- This! This! This!
Oh, I know that girl with the pigtail.
She accepted a kiss from me
with such grace.
My first kiss was gifted
straight from the lips of Sanzenin.
I'm so happy!
Oh, wait, miss.
You know that's not how it went.
I'm pleased to see you again.
Yeah, I'm sure you are.
Let's just focus
on finishing the match, okay?
- Hold on.
- The hell do you want?
Listen to me.
You're still covered in injuries.
Let me and Akane step in.
The two of us can handle the match
from here.
Got it?
Leave it to us and get out of here!
Hey!
What's going on with these two?
The audience has
suddenly started booing.
Is this in protest at a change in pairs?
I don't give a crap about who's skating.
The outfit that she's wearing isn't
hot enough.
- You're gross.
We can solve
this problem for you.
Out of nowhere, Kolkhoz High
School's Stylist Club jumps into action.
Here. Right this way, please.
- We're going to need you too.
- Uh, hey...
Yes! This one is so cute!
Wait,
I think this one looks better.
The match is resuming with
a fresh start for our handsome new pair.
Wait a minute.
I was going to pair with Akane.
Well, you're gonna have to deal with me.
Anyway, you said you already know
how to skate, didn't you?
Idiot. When do you think I've had
any time to practice?
- Huh?
- Don't worry about it.
I figured out how to stand and walk.
I'm so sorry, Akane.
I broke my promise.
I wasn't able to give you that kiss.
I don't get why you think I'd want that.
As penance, I'll take you out on a date
after the match.
Mwah.
Here, Akane. Let's pair up.
Right.
Charlotte!
You really are my Charlotte, aren't you?
Huh?
I know that collar. And I definitely gave
this to Charlotte before.
Hmph. What a wild accusation.
- Listen up, that is not my name--
- It's P-chan.
Who are you callin' P-chan?
Looks like you're still struggling
with that damage you took earlier.
Just stay down and get some rest.
Hold on.
You stay put here.
Let me be the one to deal with this.
No way! You're the person
who should be sitting this out.
How many more times do I have
to tell you I'm fine?
Nothing about you is fine right now.
I said I'm okay!
Why are you being
so stubborn about all this?
I don't know. Why are you?
- Ugh. This is why I say you're not cute.
- Hmm.
I'm doing this
because I'm worried about you.
Guess I'll go back to hating you. Hmm.
Let's get out there, Ryoga.
Huh?
Ranma.
The two of us are gonna take him down.
You okay with that, Ryoga?
Like I have a choice.
All right, cool.
We're switching out skaters.
I don't want to hear any whining.
Oh, no complaints here.
I'm flattered to find out just how far
your desire to kiss me will carry you.
It's no problem at all.
We accept your challenge.
Can't say I get what's goin' on,
but let's go, Ryoga.
Yeah!
He must be in excruciating pain.
Stupid Ranma.
Whoa!
What the hell are you doing, idiot?
I already told you,
I don't know how to skate!
- All right.
- Hmm?
Wait! Oh, no, let go of me!
Oh, this is starting off hot.
They're using the signature
Couple Crusher again.
Look at that Farewell Merry-go-Round!
Would you let go of my damn hand,
you doofus.
I'm not letting you go!
That really hurt.
There's nothing more heartbreaking
than this Merry-go-Round.
We're witnessing a deep fracture
in the sacred trust
between lovers in real time!
I don't know. I thought
they kinda hated each other.
Ha! Time to finish
this Farewell Merry-go-Round
with a flourish!
Hmph.
Whee!
What a close call that was.
I pity a poor girl like you.
To be betrayed by someone you believed in...
But you'll soon feel better.
Because after today,
I'm officially your man.
Oh! Sexy Sanzenin!
Stop daydreaming, you creep.
Get your ass up, Ryoga.
Why did this have to be on the ice?
If we didn't have to face off
in this rink, then we would win!
- Ah, that's cold!
- Water?
- Oh, I almost forgot...
- Huh?
This rink was put together
by freezing the top of a swimming pool.
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
The rink has broken apart!
Massive pieces of ice are now drifting
in different directions.
What a fool.
What do we do now, Ryoga?
Right now I'm a girl,
so I can't really say it matters to me.
I can't fall in the water.
What if I turn into a pig
in front of Akane?
Wait, so Ryoga is P-chan?
You lie? How could you do this?
But I... I never meant to lie.
You snuck into my bed.
Is that why you wanted to hide it from me
for so long?
You're gross!
I don't want you to come near me
ever again. Do you hear me?
You stupid perv!
This isn't what I wanted!
It wasn't supposed to be
this way.
Shut up!
Unpack your baggage later.
You want to let Akane see you like this?
Hmm.
Right.
Let's do what we can to finish this.
- Aw.
- Hmm.
Huh? Hmm.